format-store.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy policy

**Privacy conditions and processing of personal data**

According to the Legislative Decree n. 196 of 30th June 2003, we inform you that the personal data supplied at the moment of the registration, will be processed for the purposes of the requested service. The voluntary and express transmission of electronic mails to the addresses indicated in the various access channels to this website and the filling in of specially-made contact/request for information forms entail the subsequent acquisition of the address and data of the sender/user, which are necessary to answer the requests filed and/or provide the requested service. After the registration, according to section n. 130 paragraph 4 of D.LGS. 196/2003 we might send you e-mails regarding similar services to those supplied and you will be able to oppose to such e-mail sending in any moment. Data are collected according to the regulations of the Privacy Code, with particular attention to the minimum stardards expected (sections 33-34) as far as their treatment is concerned through IT tools (section 35), manuals and automated with closely linked logics to the purposes above mentioned and anyway in order to guarantee the security and the privacy of the data. We remind you that in any moment, you have the right to know which are the data given and how they are processed, as well as to update them, integrate them, rectify or ask for the cancellation or the block or to oppose to their processing if done in infringement with the law, according to of the section. 7 D.LGS. 196/2003, communicating it to the address [info@formatabitativi.it](mailto:info@formatabitativi.it). The data shall be processed on paper and by computer and gathered through acceptance of the on-line forms. The forms received shall be carefully stored in accordance with the law provisions on security; providing such data is mandatory, in case of refusal to provide them, this shall imply the impossibility to offer you the requested information service; such data shall not be disclosed to any third parties the data collected shall be processed by internal staff specially appointed.

Please note, lastly, that you may at any time exercise the rights under art. 7, Legislative Decree No. 196/2003 by contacting the data controller at Mobili Spinello snc - Via Giordano Bruno 13 Tetti Valfrè (TO) - Italy or by writing to the address [info@formatabitativi.it](mailto:info@formatabitativi.it)

Please refer to art. 7 of the Legislative Decree n.196/2003:

"Right of access to personal data and other rights

1\. The interested person is entitled to obtain confirmation of whether data concerning such person exist or not, even though they have not yet been recorded, as well as their communication in an intelligible form.

2\. The interested person is entitled to obtain the indication:

a) of the origin of the personal data;

b) of the processing purposes and procedures;

c) of the logic applied in case of processing made by availing of electronic tools;

d) of the identification details of the data controller, the data supervisors and of the representative appointed pursuant to article 5, subsection 2;

e) of the people or categories of people, to whom the data may be disclosed, or who may come to know such data as representatives appointed for the territory of the State, data supervisors or persons in charge.

3\. The interested person is entitled to obtain:

a) the update, correction of or, if interested, integration of the data;

b) the deletion, conversion to anonymous form or blocking of any data processed in breach of the law, including those, the storage of which is not necessary for the purposes for which the data were collected or subsequently processed;

c) a statement certifying that the operations under letters a) and b) have been made known, as to their contents, to those to whom the data had been disclosed or disseminated, unless this requirement should prove impossible or imply the use of means clearly disproportionate to the right protected.

 4\. The interested person is entitled to object, in full or in part:

a) for lawful reasons, to the processing of personal data concerning such person, even though relevant for the purpose of the collection;

b) to the processing of personal data concerning such person for purposes of transmission of advertising materials or direct sale or performance of market research or for business communication purposes".
